ntoing.com 2016-11-25

# 

**Source / Credit?**

We respect originality and creativity. Please cite the source or give correct credit whenever you can.

**Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, Ntoing collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request.Ntoing’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Ntoing s visitors use its website. From time to time, Ntoing may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g. by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Ntoing also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. 9GAG does not use such information to identify its visitors, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Ntoing s websites choose to interact with Ntoing in ways that require Ntoing to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Ntoing gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for Ntoing com to provide a username and email address. In each case, Ntoing collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Ntoing. Ntoing does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**

Ntoing may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Ntoing may monitor the most popular collections on Ntoing com. Ntoing may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Ntoing does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Ntoing uses cookies to help Ntoing identify and track visitors, their usage of Ntoing websites, and their website access preferences. Ntoing visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Ntoing s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Ntoing’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Ads**

Ads appearing on any Ntoing websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by Ntoing and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Links to Third Party Sites**

This privacy policy only applies to information collected by Ntoing This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Ntoing does not own or control, or employees that Ntoing does not manage. A Ntoing website may contain links to third party websites. Any information you provide to, or that is collected by, third-party sites may be subject to the privacy policies of those sites, if any. We encourage you to read such privacy policies of any third-party sites you visit. It is the sole responsibility of such third parties to adhere to any applicable restrictions on the disclosure of your personally-identifying information, and 9GAG and its affiliates shall not be liable for wrongful use or disclosure of your personally-identifying information by any third party.

**Security**

All non-personally-identifying information, potentially personally-identifying and personally identifying-information described above is stored on restricted database servers.

**Choice/Opt-out**

If we ever send you information by email concerning new products, services or information that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an email address by which you may request no further notices.

**Address Book Data**

Any external address book data (email contacts, etc.) that a user voluntarily gives Ntoing access to will only be used for the described feature (looking up friends, etc.), and will not be stored or repurposed.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Ntoing may change its privacy policy from time to time, and in Ntoing s sole discretion. v encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its privacy policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this privacy policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our sites in general, please contact us.
